Guilty is that witch
有罪的是那个女巫
who has seduced a monk
她诱惑了一位修士
and has practiced her diabolical ritual within this hallowed place.
并在这神圣之地举行了她的邪恶仪式
Guilty is Salvatore
有罪的是萨尔瓦托雷
who has confessed to his heretical past
他承认了自己的异端过往
and was caught in flagrante delicto with a witch!
并与女巫当场被抓
Guilty is Remigio de Varagine
有罪的是雷米吉奥·德·瓦拉吉纳
who, in addition to being unrepentant of his heresies
他不仅对异端罪行毫无悔意
was caught attempting to escape after murdering Severinus.
还在谋杀塞维里努斯后企图逃跑
That's a lie!
那是谎言
I never killed the herbalist or anyone else in this abbey!
我从未杀死草药师或修道院里的任何人
I therefore request you
因此我请求您
to confirm my sentence, my lord abbot.
确认我的判决 院长大人
My heart is filled with sorrow
我心中充满悲伤
but I can find no reason to contest
但我找不到任何理由质疑
the just sentence of the Holy Inquisition.
神圣宗教裁判所的公正判决
And you, William of Baskerville?
你呢 巴斯克维尔的威廉
Yes.
是的
He is guilty.
他有罪
Guilty of having, in his youth
有罪于他在年轻时
misinterpreted the message of the gospels.
误解了福音的信息
And he is guilty of having confused
他有罪于混淆了
the love of poverty with the blind destruction of wealth and property.
对贫穷的热爱与对财富和财产的盲目破坏
But, my lord abbot, he is innocent of the crimes
但是 院长大人 他对那些罪行是无辜的
that have bathed your abbey in blood.
那些让您的修道院血流成河的罪行
For Brother Remigio cannot read Greek.
因为雷米吉奥兄弟不识希腊文
And this entire mystery
而这整个谜团
hinges on the theft and possession of a book written in Greek
都围绕着一本希腊文著作的盗窃与占有
and hidden in some secret part of the library.
它被藏在图书馆的某个隐秘之处
Since the verdict of the Inquisition has been disputed by brother William
既然宗教裁判所的判决受到质疑
we are obliged to extract the prisoner's confession to murder.
我们有责任让囚犯承认谋杀
Take him to the forge and show him the instruments.
把他带到锻造室 让他看看刑具
I'll confess anything you want
我愿意承认你们想要的一切
but don't torture me.
但不要折磨我
I can't live through it, not like Salvatore.
我承受不了 不像萨尔瓦托雷那样
Very well.
很好
Why did you kill them?
你为什么要杀他们
Why?
为什么
I don't know why.
我不知道为什么
- Because you were inspired by the devil? - Yes.
- 因为你是受魔鬼唆使 - 是的
That's it. I was inspired by the devil.
就是这样 我是受魔鬼唆使
I am inspired by the devil!
我是受魔鬼唆使
Adrammelech, Lucifer, I summon you, lords of hell!
阿德拉梅莱克 路西法 我召唤你们 地狱之主
Alastor!
阿拉斯托
Azazel!
阿萨兹勒
The shepherd has done his duty
牧羊人已尽其职
and the infected sheep must now be consigned to the purifying flame.
感染的羊群现在必须被交给净化之火
You may burn Brother Remigio
你可以烧死雷米吉奥兄弟
but you will not stop the crimes being committed in this abbey.
但你无法阻止这修道院里正在发生的罪行
Other monks will meet their deaths here
还会有其他修士在此丧命
and they also will have blackened fingers
他们的手指也会发黑
and blackened tongues!
舌头也会发黑